Finding aid of the Herbert Hutchinson Brimley Photograph Collection, 1880-1977 PHC.42
State Archives of North Carolina
- Birds, PhC.42.Birds; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Royal Terns, Royal Shoals, Hyde Co., NC, 1939. (7n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F41-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bird Colonies on Shoals, Hyde Co., NC, 1909. (4n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F42-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bird Colonies on Shoals, Hyde Co., NC, 1909. (4n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F42-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bird Colonies on Shoals, Hyde Co., NC, 1909. (4n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F42-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bird Colonies on Shoals, Hyde Co., NC, 1909. (4n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F42-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bald Eagle, Angier, NC, 1940. (5n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F43-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bald Eagle, Angier, NC, 1940. (5n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F43-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bald Eagle, Angier, NC, 1940. (5n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F43-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bald Eagle, Angier, NC, 1940. (5n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F43-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bald Eagle, Angier, NC, 1940. (5n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F43-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sea Gulls at the beach, n.d., PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F44; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Paroquet Case, PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F45-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hoatzin Case, PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F45-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Indicator birds, African honeyguides case, PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F45-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bird case, Peabody Museum, PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F46; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Decoy Geese in a pen. (4), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F47-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Decoy Geese in a pen. (4), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F47-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Decoy Geese in a pen. (4), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F47-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Decoy Geese in a pen. (4), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F47-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Ducks, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F48; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds collected by T. W. Addickes, Southport, NC, 1913. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F49-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds collected by T. W. Addickes, Southport, NC, 1913. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F49-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pied billed Grebe, ca. 1912. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Osprey Nests, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F50; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Red-Cockaded Woodpecker, Orton Pond, 1920. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F51; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Person kneeling with bird., PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F52; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Man kneeling with pelican., PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F53; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pied billed Grebe, ca. 1912. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pied billed Grebe, ca. 1912. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Live buzzard young, ca. 1915. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Live turkey buzzard young, ca. 1915. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Birds.F9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Boats and Boating, PhC.42.Boats; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Boating Locks, n.d., PhC.42.Bx5.Boats.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dug-out Cypress Boat, Bridgeton, NC, 1944. (2), PhC.42.Bx5.Boats.F2-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dug-out Cypress Boat, Bridgeton, NC, 1944. (2), PhC.42.Bx5.Boats.F2-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Fishing Boats, n.d., PhC.42.Bx5.Boats.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Fishing Boats at dock, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx5.Boats.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fish Mullets, Beaufort, NC, n.d. (LS), PhC.42.Bx5.Boats.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Menhaden Fishery, near Beaufort, NC. (LS), PhC.42.Bx5.Boats.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fleet of wrecked boats, Hatteras, NC. ca. 1899, PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster Boats, Cape Hatteras, c. 1900-1903., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster Fleet, Washington, NC, ca. 1890. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F12-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster Fleet, Washington, NC, ca. 1890. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F12-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster Cannery, Washington, NC ca. 1884., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster House and Boats, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Water Front, Belhaven, NC. (1) (1n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Ship built by J. J. Davis, Buxton, NC, ca. 1908., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster House, Belhaven, NC. (1) (1n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two Masted Vessel, Julia Bell, ca. 1880s., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wreck of the Priscilla, Hatteras, NC, 1899. Rasmus Midgett sits on wreckage of the Priscilla. He single-handedly saved ten people from this ship during the hurricane. The San Ciriaco hurricane was the longest-lived Atlantic storm ever tracked. (SEE NOTES, PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Oyster boat, Washington, NC, 1884., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pound Net Boat, Albemarle Sound, 1884. (1) (1n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Boat, c. 1900., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Three men aboard a vessel, c. 1890s. (N.83.6.181), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pamlico River at Chocowinity, NC, c. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F24; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Boating on a bend of the Roanoke River, c. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F25; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shipping cotton bales, New Bern, NC. (1) (1n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F26; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Boating on Lake Ellis, c. 1910., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F27; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "New Berne" steamer, Pamlico Sound, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F28; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dock at New Bern, NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F29; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steamer Boat, Cape Fear River, 1910. (2) (5n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F30-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steamer Boat, Cape Fear River, 1910. (2) (5n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F30-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steamer Boat, Cape Fear River, 1910. (2) (5n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F30-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steamer Boat, Cape Fear River, 1910. (2) (5n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F30-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steamer Boat, Cape Fear River, 1910. (2) (5n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F30-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steamer Boat, Cape Fear River, 1910. (2) (5n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F30-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Steamer Boat, Cape Fear River, 1910. (2) (5n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F30-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sailing Skiff, Cape Hatteras, NC, 1900-1903., PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sprunt Speed Boat, Orton Plantation, ca. 1920. (4) (2n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F8-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sprunt Speed Boat, Orton Plantation, ca. 1920. (4) (2n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F8-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sprunt Speed Boat, Orton Plantation, ca. 1920. (4) (2n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F8-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sprunt Speed Boat, Orton Plantation, ca. 1920. (4) (2n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F8-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sunken Boat, Southport, NC, ca. 1913. (2) (1n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F9-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Sunken Boat, Southport, NC, ca. 1913. (2) (1n), PhC.42.Bx6.Boats.F9-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Bodies of Water, PhC.42.BodiesofWater; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lake Scene, Craven Co., NC., PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lake James, 1925, PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F2-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lake James, 1925, PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F2-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lake James, 1925; Lake, Raleigh Country Club, 1914. (5), PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F2-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lake, Raleigh Country Club, 1914. (5), PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F2-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified pond or lake., PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - South Toe River, Mitchell Co., NC., PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Co., Roanoke Rapids, NC. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F5-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Co., Roanoke Rapids, NC. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.BodiesofWater.F5-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Botanical Specimens, PhC.42.BotanicalSpec; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Possibly catching butterflies, Wake Co., NC, PhC.42.Bx6.BotanicalSpec.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bark Specimen, Raleigh, NC, 1914, PhC.42.Bx6.BotanicalSpec.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bark Specimen, Raleigh, NC, 1914, PhC.42.Bx6.BotanicalSpec.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bark Specimen, Raleigh, NC, 1914, PhC.42.Bx6.BotanicalSpec.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Bogue Sound and Banks, PhC.42.BogueSound; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bogue Sound and Banks Investigating Party, 1912. (7n), PhC.42.Bx6.BogueSound.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bogue Sound and Banks Investigating Party, 1912. (7n), PhC.42.Bx6.BogueSound.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bogue Sound and Banks Investigating Party, 1912. (7n), PhC.42.Bx6.BogueSound.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bogue Sound and Banks Investigating Party, 1912. (7n), PhC.42.Bx6.BogueSound.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bogue Sound and Banks Investigating Party, 1912. (7n), PhC.42.Bx6.BogueSound.F1-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bogue Sound and Banks Investigating Party, 1912. (7n), PhC.42.Bx6.BogueSound.F1-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bogue Sound and Banks Investigating Party, 1912. (7n), PhC.42.Bx6.BogueSound.F1-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Bridges, PhC.42.Bridges; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Railroad Bridge, Roanoke Rapids, NC, 1890., PhC.42.Bx6.Bridges.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Bridge, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx6.Bridges.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Bridge construction, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx6.Bridges.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Railroad Bridge, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.Bx6.Bridges.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Creek Bridge, ca. 1900., PhC.42.Bx6.Bridges.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- C. S. Brimley, PhC.42.BrimleyCS; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley at work, History Museum, 1942, PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyCS.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - co.'s. Brimley at work, History Museum, 1942, PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyCS.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Portrait, ca. 1940s. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyCS.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- H. H. Brimley, PhC.42.BrimleyHH; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Den curtains, H. H. Brimley house. (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F10-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Den curtains, H. H. Brimley house. (2) (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F10-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Arthur and Bob Brimley. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H.H. Brimley and C.S. Brimley performing Taxidermy, ca. 1940s. (3n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hall IV, History Museum, ca. 1942. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H.H. Brimley and C.S. Brimley performing Taxidermy, ca. 1940s. (3n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley Family at Salem, Mass., 1932. (7), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F13-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley Family at Salem, Mass., 1932. (7), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F13-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley Family at Salem, Mass., 1932. (7), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F13-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley Family at Salem, Mass., 1932. (7), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F13-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley Family at Salem, Mass., 1932. (7), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F13-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley Family at Salem, Mass., 1932. (7), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F13-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Brimley Family at Salem, Mass., 1932. (7), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F13-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - College girls on a milk wagon, Vermont, ca. 1906., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mr. and Mrs. Brimley canoeing., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley, ca. 1944. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F16-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley, ca. 1944. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F16-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Neuse River, Wake Co., NC, ca. 1900., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whiskey still, State museum, 1928. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley in a heron habitat, Orton Pond., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Display table of apples., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Work Room, H. H. Brimley showing birds, etc., ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Residence of H. H. Brimley, 1910. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Residence of H. H. Brimley, 1910. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley performing taxidermy on a panther, ca. 1900. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley performing taxidermy on a glossy Ibis, 1942. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F24-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley performing taxidermy on a glossy Ibis, 1942. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F24-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley performing taxidermy on a glossy Ibis, 1942. (3) (enlarged section of f24-2), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F24-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mr. and Mrs. Brimley fishing. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F25-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mr. and Mrs. Brimley fishing. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F25-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Mr. and Mrs. Brimley fishing. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F25-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley working on a basking shark, ca. 1940s., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F26; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley performing taxidermy on a panther, ca. 1900. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F27-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley performing taxidermy on a panther, ca. 1900. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F27-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley seated at his desk, ca. 1920., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F28; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley working on a model of True's Beaked Whale, 1944. (4), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F29; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley in his office, ca. 1920. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley on Smith's Island, NC., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F30; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley with model of a Black Marlin, History Museum, ca. 1943., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F31; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley and family at Wray Villa, Cane River, ca. 1903., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F32; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley with a model of a Pea Hen, History Museum, ca. 1937., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F33; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley at the St. Louis Exposition, Alaska Exhibit, 1904. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F35-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley at the St. Louis Exposition, Alaska Exhibit, 1904. (3), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F35-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley, portrait by Siddell Studio, June, 1931., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F36; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - The Brimley brothers, Fred, H. H., and C. S., Fred remained in England while the other two wrought their fortunes in North Carolina. This picture was made during Fred's only visit to Raleigh, 1937., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F37; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley with a mounted elk and buffalo, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F38; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley and Harry T. Davis working on the History Museum Fish Exhibit. (5), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F39; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley home, Raleigh, NC, ca. 1923. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley performing taxidermy, ca. 1940s. (2), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F40; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley, F. Sherman, and C. S. Brimley at Great Lake, NC, 1912., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F41; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Canoe in a creek, Camp Bryan, Lake Ellis, Craven County, NC, May, 1906., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley showing servicemen a great mammoth specimen, ca. 1940s., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F43; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley canoeing, New River, ca. 1920. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H.H. Brimley in his office., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F6-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H.H. Brimley in his office., PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F6-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H.H. Brimley performing taxidermy, 1942. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H.H. Brimley and others, Battery Island, 1938.(2) (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - H. H. Brimley house, Raleigh, NC, 1908. (n), PhC.42.Bx6.BrimleyHH.F9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Business and Industry, PhC.42.BusAndIndustry; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Old Mountain Water Mill, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1900., PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Badin Power Plant excavation, ca. 1904., PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dunn's Cannery, New Bern, NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Borden Brick and Tile Co., Sanford, NC, ca. 1926 (2n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F12-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Borden Brick and Tile Co., Sanford, NC, ca. 1926 (2n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F12-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Isenhour Brick and Tile Co., ca. 1927 (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F12-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Power Station, Raleigh, NC vicinity. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F12-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Ive's Canning Factory, Newport NC. (1) (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Co. Dam, Stanly Co., NC (n) (2), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Co. Dam, Stanly Co., NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Co., General View, Stanly Co., NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Co. Dam, Stanly Co., NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Co. Dam, Stanly Co., NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Co. Dam, Stanly Co., NC. (2), PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Whitney Co. Dam, Stanly Co., NC, ca. 1903., PhC.42.Bx7.BusAndIndstry.F9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Camps and Camping, PhC.42.Camping; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camping Party, Big Bald, Yancey Co., NC., PhC.42.Bx7.Camping.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camping scene, Wake Co., NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.Camping.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Cape Hatteras, PhC.42.CapeHatteras; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Beach Cart, Cape Hatteras, NC, ca. 1902., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Weather Station, Hatteras Village., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Surf at Cape Hatteras, NC, 1906. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Surf near Cape Hatteras, NC, 1906. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Surf near Cape Hatteras, NC, 1906. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Surf near Cape Hatteras, NC, 1906. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Surf near Cape Hatteras, NC, 1906. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Surf near Cape Hatteras, NC, 1906. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Surf near Cape Hatteras, NC, 1906. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified people on a farm, Cape Hatteras, NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wild Geese captured at Cape Hatteras, NC., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Geese, Cow, and Chickens, Cape Hatteras, ca. 1900-1903., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Turkey, Cape Hatteras, ca. 1900-1903., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Palmettos near the beach, Cape Hatteras, NC, ca. 1905. (2), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F22-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Palmettos near the beach, Cape Hatteras, NC, ca. 1905. (2), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F22-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dogwood trees, Cape Hatteras, NC, 1904., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified home and family, Cape Hatteras, NC., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F24; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Captain Stowe's Home, Cape Hatteras, NC., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F25; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cape Hatteras Lighthouse, ca. 1905., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F26; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified house, Cape Hatteras, NC, ca. 1900., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F27; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Nase Jennette, game warden, Cape Hatteras, NC, ca. 1900-1905., PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F28; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fisherman/Coast Guardsman, Cape Hatteras, NC, 1901. (2), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F29; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Banks Oak, Cape Hatteras, NC, ca. 1905 (n), PhC.42.Bx7.CapeHatteras.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946